by RentAnAdviser.com
Just a young gun with a quick fuse
I was uptight‚ wanna let loose
I was dreaming of bigger things and
Wanna leave my own life behind
Not a yes sir‚ not a follower
Fit the box‚ fit the mold
Have a seat in the foyer‚
take a number
I was lightning before the thunder
Thunder‚ thunder
Thunder‚ thun ‚ thunder
Thun thun thunder‚ thunder‚ thunder
Thun thun thunder‚ thunder
Thunder‚ feel the thunder
Lightning and the thunder
Thunder‚ thunder
Thunder
Kids were laughing in my classes
While I was scheming for the masses
Who do you think you are?
Dreaming ′bout being a big star
You say You are basic‚
you say You are easy
You are always riding in the back seat
Now I am smiling from the stage while
You were clapping in the nose bleeds
Thunder
Thunder‚ thun ‚ thunder
Thun thun thunder‚ thunder‚ thunder
Thun thun thunder‚ thunder
Thunder‚ feel the thunder
Lightning and the thunder
Thunder
Thunder‚ feel the thunder
Lightning and the thunder‚ thunder
Thunder‚ thunder‚ thunder
Thun thun thunder‚ thunder
by RentAnAdviser.com